[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Can you hear me?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "hear", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "But both of you, tell me first, are you OK?", "question_tokens": ["But", "both", "of", "you", ",", "tell", "me", "first", ",", "are", "you", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Did you have any warning that something was wrong with the plane?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "warning", "that", "something", "was", "wrong", "with", "the", "plane", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "The flight was a little rocky from the start but nobody thought really anything of it.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "flight", "was", "a", "little", "rocky", "from", "the", "start", "but", "nobody", "thought", "really", "anything", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "So no announcement from the cockpit that you remember, Frank?", "question_tokens": ["So", "no", "announcement", "from", "the", "cockpit", "that", "you", "remember", ",", "Frank", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Dominique, do you remember any announcement other than to check your seatbelts?", "question_tokens": ["Dominique", ",", "do", "you", "remember", "any", "announcement", "other", "than", "to", "check", "your", "seatbelts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes, but, you know, it kind of struck us as a little odd, because they did also say to check your neighbor's seatbelts as well.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "kind", "of", "struck", "us", "as", "a", "little", "odd", ",", "because", "they", "did", "also", "say", "to", "check", "your", "neighbor", "'s", "seatbelts", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "What does it feel like in the plane, Dominique?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "feel", "like", "in", "the", "plane", ",", "Dominique", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, it was incredibly shocking.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "incredibly", "shocking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dominique"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "What happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Well, none of the masks dropped, but, you know, we were -- it was very -- yes, I mean, we were very shaken.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "none", "of", "the", "masks", "dropped", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "were", "--", "it", "was", "very", "--", "yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "we", "were", "very", "shaken", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "How long do you think it took you, Dominique, to stop?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "do", "you", "think", "it", "took", "you", ",", "Dominique", ",", "to", "stop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "I mean, it felt like forever to be honest with you because it does seemed like we were traveling so fast.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "felt", "like", "forever", "to", "be", "honest", "with", "you", "because", "it", "does", "seemed", "like", "we", "were", "traveling", "so", "fast", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dominique"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Dominique, where were you?", "question_tokens": ["Dominique", ",", "where", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "We were probably seven or eight rows down, just in front of the wing.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "were", "probably", "seven", "or", "eight", "rows", "down", ",", "just", "in", "front", "of", "the", "wing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "Did you see people injured there?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "see", "people", "injured", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I didn't see anybody injured.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "see", "anybody", "injured", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "When they finally gave you word, what did they say and what happened?", "question_tokens": ["When", "they", "finally", "gave", "you", "word", ",", "what", "did", "they", "say", "and", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Well, you know, immediately people were trying to jump out of their seatbelts and get off.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "immediately", "people", "were", "trying", "to", "jump", "out", "of", "their", "seatbelts", "and", "get", "off", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 99, "question": "And then, Frank, you wound up going off a slide, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", ",", "Frank", ",", "you", "wound", "up", "going", "off", "a", "slide", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "I looked outside and like I see that the emergency vehicles were surrounding the plane and they were, you know, hosing it down, and then at that point people really started kind of getting irritated and asking, you know, for the --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "looked", "outside", "and", "like", "I", "see", "that", "the", "emergency", "vehicles", "were", "surrounding", "the", "plane", "and", "they", "were", ",", "you", "know", ",", "hosing", "it", "down", ",", "and", "then", "at", "that", "point", "people", "really", "started", "kind", "of", "getting", "irritated", "and", "asking", ",", "you", "know", ",", "for", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Frank, are you still there?", "question_tokens": ["Frank", ",", "are", "you", "still", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "How did you get off the plane?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "off", "the", "plane", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "But do all your loved ones know that you're OK, Frank and Dominique?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "all", "your", "loved", "ones", "know", "that", "you", "'re", "OK", ",", "Frank", "and", "Dominique", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "DT", "PRP$", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dominique"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "The combination of more media access and this particular royal couple wanting to do it their own way?", "question_tokens": ["The", "combination", "of", "more", "media", "access", "and", "this", "particular", "royal", "couple", "wanting", "to", "do", "it", "their", "own", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "So that fact, Victoria, do you think that changes the equation here and maybe opens a possibility for somewhat of a sunset?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "fact", ",", "Victoria", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "changes", "the", "equation", "here", "and", "maybe", "opens", "a", "possibility", "for", "somewhat", "of", "a", "sunset", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "No, all I think it does is show the queen that her 61 years of service and duty have been worth every second.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "all", "I", "think", "it", "does", "is", "show", "the", "queen", "that", "her", "61", "years", "of", "service", "and", "duty", "have", "been", "worth", "every", "second", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Victoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Do you think there's a recognition, though, of how much energy William, especially with his marriage to Kate and now this little boy whatever his name will be, has given to the resurgence of popularity of the monarchy that might figure into who they want up front?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "recognition", ",", "though", ",", "of", "how", "much", "energy", "William", ",", "especially", "with", "his", "marriage", "to", "Kate", "and", "now", "this", "little", "boy", "whatever", "his", "name", "will", "be", ",", "has", "given", "to", "the", "resurgence", "of", "popularity", "of", "the", "monarchy", "that", "might", "figure", "into", "who", "they", "want", "up", "front", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William", "Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "But is there a feel there in this event of Diana's presence, her significance with Williams?", "question_tokens": ["But", "is", "there", "a", "feel", "there", "in", "this", "event", "of", "Diana", "'s", "presence", ",", "her", "significance", "with", "Williams", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "You know, I think everybody in the back of their minds always thinks about that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "everybody", "in", "the", "back", "of", "their", "minds", "always", "thinks", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Williams"], "LOCATION": ["Diana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "What do you think this will mean going-forward in terms of how much focus will be on this new family?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "this", "will", "mean", "going-forward", "in", "terms", "of", "how", "much", "focus", "will", "be", "on", "this", "new", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Well, I think longevity and stability and continuity.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "longevity", "and", "stability", "and", "continuity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana"]}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "What do you think that will mean in terms of the decisions he and his wife will make and how they raise their little boy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "that", "will", "mean", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "decisions", "he", "and", "his", "wife", "will", "make", "and", "how", "they", "raise", "their", "little", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, I think that Diana paved the way in many ways because she went against the grain so much, she was so determined to do things differently.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "Diana", "paved", "the", "way", "in", "many", "ways", "because", "she", "went", "against", "the", "grain", "so", "much", ",", "she", "was", "so", "determined", "to", "do", "things", "differently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "This could very well be a different lifestyle because of that early influence, is that what you're saying?", "question_tokens": ["This", "could", "very", "well", "be", "a", "different", "lifestyle", "because", "of", "that", "early", "influence", ",", "is", "that", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "Yes, I think it's exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry"]}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Not so much because of the succession, but that media spotlight may free him up a little bit?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "so", "much", "because", "of", "the", "succession", ",", "but", "that", "media", "spotlight", "may", "free", "him", "up", "a", "little", "bit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Well, I think probably -- and Prince Harry will be absolutely delighted this evening with the news he's an uncle.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "probably", "--", "and", "Prince", "Harry", "will", "be", "absolutely", "delighted", "this", "evening", "with", "the", "news", "he", "'s", "an", "uncle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George", "Arthur"]}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "But give me your take, what's the name going to be?", "question_tokens": ["But", "give", "me", "your", "take", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "name", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Ooh, I think my money's on George and Arthur somewhere in there.", "answer_tokens": ["Ooh", ",", "I", "think", "my", "money", "'s", "on", "George", "and", "Arthur", "somewhere", "in", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bruno"]}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Nothing?", "question_tokens": ["Nothing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "No, I don't think we're going to be hearing Bruno or Barack.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "hearing", "Bruno", "or", "Barack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "No, nothing?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "nothing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Well, I think he's discussing it with them at the moment, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "discussing", "it", "with", "them", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris"]}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Is there a little bit of that in you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "that", "in", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Yes, there is, Chris.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "there", "is", ",", "Chris", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "So that would have been -- will (ph) exciting about this little girl, yes?", "question_tokens": ["So", "that", "would", "have", "been", "--", "will", "(", "ph", ")", "exciting", "about", "this", "little", "girl", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ":", "MD", "VB", "NN", ":", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "How do you think he will choose to raise his little boy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "will", "choose", "to", "raise", "his", "little", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Chris, I -- I know his father well.", "answer_tokens": ["Chris", ",", "I", "--", "I", "know", "his", "father", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William", "Kate", "William", "Kate"]}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Do you think this will be a kid that will be thrust out there as look at the new royal or more of an accommodation of private and public?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "this", "will", "be", "a", "kid", "that", "will", "be", "thrust", "out", "there", "as", "look", "at", "the", "new", "royal", "or", "more", "of", "an", "accommodation", "of", "private", "and", "public", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "Since William and Kate got married, we've seen William be incredibly protective of Kate.", "answer_tokens": ["Since", "William", "and", "Kate", "got", "married", ",", "we", "'ve", "seen", "William", "be", "incredibly", "protective", "of", "Kate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Do they -- does the person need medical attention?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "--", "does", "the", "person", "need", "medical", "attention", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "I don't know, they're getting him out of the car right now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "they", "'re", "getting", "him", "out", "of", "the", "car", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "And this in the same area where everything else happened, true?", "question_tokens": ["And", "this", "in", "the", "same", "area", "where", "everything", "else", "happened", ",", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NN", "RB", "VBD", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Yes, very strange.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "very", "strange", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "We had conversations over the last few days.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "conversations", "over", "the", "last", "few", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Do -- do you believe he is safe there in Sanford?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "--", "do", "you", "believe", "he", "is", "safe", "there", "in", "Sanford", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "EX", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "'MARA: Well, that was only a few days after he was trying to make some plans and decided what to do.", "answer_tokens": ["'MARA", ":", "Well", ",", "that", "was", "only", "a", "few", "days", "after", "he", "was", "trying", "to", "make", "some", "plans", "and", "decided", "what", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sanford"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "I mean, you -- you have said, and we've heard through the family that there have been meaningful threats against his safety, yes?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "--", "you", "have", "said", ",", "and", "we", "'ve", "heard", "through", "the", "family", "that", "there", "have", "been", "meaningful", "threats", "against", "his", "safety", ",", "yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Yes, there have been.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "there", "have", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "President Obama in his comments -- what have you thought about all this?", "question_tokens": ["President", "Obama", "in", "his", "comments", "--", "what", "have", "you", "thought", "about", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, you know, if you look at just the sound bite, I think it was -- it was inappropriate to suggest to suggest that 35 years ago, he could have -- Trayvon could have been him or whatever.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "you", "look", "at", "just", "the", "sound", "bite", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "--", "it", "was", "inappropriate", "to", "suggest", "to", "suggest", "that", "35", "years", "ago", ",", "he", "could", "have", "--", "Trayvon", "could", "have", "been", "him", "or", "whatever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "And you acknowledge that but you have an explanation, which is?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "acknowledge", "that", "but", "you", "have", "an", "explanation", ",", "which", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "The reality is, is that what George did was not just legally correct, but was appropriate for the situation that he was in.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "reality", "is", ",", "is", "that", "what", "George", "did", "was", "not", "just", "legally", "correct", ",", "but", "was", "appropriate", "for", "the", "situation", "that", "he", "was", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "But do you think that this case is a legitimate starting- off point for discussions about concealed weapon laws and stand-your- ground?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "that", "this", "case", "is", "a", "legitimate", "starting-", "off", "point", "for", "discussions", "about", "concealed", "weapon", "laws", "and", "stand-your-", "ground", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Well, again, this is not a stand-your-ground case, never was.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "this", "is", "not", "a", "stand-your-ground", "case", ",", "never", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What are our big moments tomorrow?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "our", "big", "moments", "tomorrow", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Well, hopefully, the family is getting some rest tonight, their first night -- night with a new baby of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "hopefully", ",", "the", "family", "is", "getting", "some", "rest", "tonight", ",", "their", "first", "night", "--", "night", "with", "a", "new", "baby", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "What about the name?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "the", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Name -- who knows.", "answer_tokens": ["Name", "--", "who", "knows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "You're really a priest and an expert, though, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "really", "a", "priest", "and", "an", "expert", ",", "though", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "That's right, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "And you saw what happened out there today, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "saw", "what", "happened", "out", "there", "today", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130722pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "But should he be in charge of security when it only takes one bad person?", "question_tokens": ["But", "should", "he", "be", "in", "charge", "of", "security", "when", "it", "only", "takes", "one", "bad", "person", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Well, first of all, he is not in charge of his security.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "he", "is", "not", "in", "charge", "of", "his", "security", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]